

SHAKIL MIAH

Web Designer

About me

I am a talented, ambitious and hardworking individual, with broad skills and experience in frontend development. I am deeply addicted to HTML5 and CSS3 .I work professionally because coding is passion and i am passionate about that .

Contact

01943764283 shakilrafi1030@gmail. com

Mohammadpur Dhaka, ST 1207

Expertise

- HTML
- CSS
- BOOTSTRAP!
- JAVASCRPT
- JQUERY

Education

Purbanow doba public high school
Shariatpur St., Dhaka, ST 1207

2020- 2021 BK Nogor college Shariatpur St., Dhaka, ST 1207

Work Experience

2021-2022

- Freelance work at online marketplace
- Freelance work at Local marketplace
- 2019-2020
 - I Worked passionately in customer service in a highvolume office.
 - Completed the F.A.S.T. customer service training class.
 - I Maintained a high tip average thanks to consistent customer satisfaction.